<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<root>
	<item type="dict">
		<rank type="str">1</rank>
		<french_name type="str">Université de Kinshasa</french_name>
		<location type="str">Kinshasa</location>
		<faculties type="list">
			<item type="str">Faculty of Agronomy </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Economics </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Law </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Medicine and Dentistry </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Pharmacy </item>
			<item type="str"> Polytechnic </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Science</item>
		</faculties>
		<postal_code type="str">Boîte Postale 125</postal_code>
		<telephone type="str"> +243 (89) 892 0507</telephone>
		<description type="str">Established in 1954,  Université de Kinshasa (University of Kinshasa) is a non-profit public higher-education institution located in the large metropolis of Kinshasa (population range of over 5,000,000 inhabitants).   Officially recognized by the Ministère de l'Enseignement Supérieur et Universitaire, République Démocratique du Congo (Ministry of Higher and University Education of the Democratic Republic of the Congo), Université de Kinshasa (UNIKIN) is a large (uniRank enrollment range: 25,000-29,999 students) coeducational Congolese higher education institution. Université de Kinshasa (UNIKIN) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study matrix below for further details.  UNIKIN also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library,  as well as administrative services.</description>
		<name type="str">University of Kinshasa</name>
		<acronym type="str">UNIKIN</acronym>
		<founded type="str">1954</founded>
	</item>
	<item type="dict">
		<rank type="str">2</rank>
		<french_name type="str">Université de Lubumbashi</french_name>
		<location type="str">Lubumbashi</location>
		<faculties type="list">
			<item type="str">Faculty of Agronomy </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Economics </item>
			<item type="str"> Higher Institute of Medical Techniques </item>
			<item type="str"> Higher School of Commerce </item>
			<item type="str"> Higher School of Engineering </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Law </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Letters </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Medicine </item>
			<item type="str"> Polytechnic </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Psychology and Educational Science</item>
		</faculties>
		<postal_code type="str">Boîte Postale 1825</postal_code>
		<telephone type="str"> +243 (99) 719 7767</telephone>
		<description type="str">Established in 1955,  Université de Lubumbashi (University of Lubumbashi) is a non-profit public higher-education institution located in the metropolis of Lubumbashi (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Haut-Katanga.   Officially recognized by the Ministère de l'Enseignement Supérieur et Universitaire, République Démocratique du Congo (Ministry of Higher and University Education of the Democratic Republic of the Congo), Université de Lubumbashi (UNILU) is a large (uniRank enrollment range: 10,000-14,999 students) coeducational Congolese higher education institution. Université de Lubumbashi (UNILU) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study matrix below for further details. This 65 years old Congolese higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations.  UNILU also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library,  as well as administrative services.</description>
		<name type="str">University of Lubumbashi</name>
		<acronym type="str">UNILU</acronym>
		<founded type="str">1955</founded>
	</item>
	<item type="dict">
		<rank type="str">3</rank>
		<french_name type="str">Université Protestante du Congo</french_name>
		<location type="str">Kinshasa</location>
		<faculties type="list">
			<item type="str">Faculty of Business/Economics </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Law </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Medicine </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Theology</item>
		</faculties>
		<postal_code type="str">Boîte Postale 4745</postal_code>
		<telephone type="str"> +243 (88) 46122</telephone>
		<description type="str">Founded in 1959,  Université Protestante du Congo (Protestant University of Congo) is a  private higher-education institution located in the large metropolis of Kinshasa (population range of over 5,000,000 inhabitants).   Officially recognized by the Ministère de l'Enseignement Supérieur et Universitaire, République Démocratique du Congo (Ministry of Higher and University Education of the Democratic Republic of the Congo), Université Protestante du Congo (UPC) is a medium-sized (uniRank enrollment range: 7,000-7,999 students) coeducational Congolese higher education institution formally affiliated with the Christian-Protestant religion. Université Protestante du Congo (UPC) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study matrix below for further details.  UPC also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library,  sports facilities,  as well as administrative services.</description>
		<name type="str">Protestant University of Congo</name>
		<acronym type="str">UPC</acronym>
		<founded type="str">1959</founded>
	</item>
	<item type="dict">
		<rank type="str">4</rank>
		<french_name type="str">Université de Kindu</french_name>
		<location type="str">Kindu</location>
		<faculties type="null"/>
		<postal_code type="str">Site universitaire de LWAMA</postal_code>
		<telephone type="str"> +243 (81) 418 4281</telephone>
		<description type="str">Founded in 2005,  Université de Kindu (University of Kindu) is a non-profit public higher-education institution located in the small city of Kindu (population range of 50,000-249,999 inhabitants), Maniema.   Officially recognized by the Ministère de l'Enseignement Supérieur et Universitaire, République Démocratique du Congo (Ministry of Higher and University Education of the Democratic Republic of the Congo), Université de Kindu (UNIKI) is a coeducational Congolese higher education institution. Université de Kindu (UNIKI) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study matrix below for further details.  UNIKI also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library,  as well as administrative services.</description>
		<name type="str">University of Kindu</name>
		<acronym type="str">UNIKI</acronym>
		<founded type="str">2005</founded>
	</item>
	<item type="dict">
		<rank type="str">5</rank>
		<french_name type="str">Université Protestante de Lubumbashi</french_name>
		<location type="str">Lubumbashi</location>
		<faculties type="list">
			<item type="str">Faculty of Computer Science </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Theology </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Information and Communication Sciences </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Economy and Management Science </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Letter and Human Science </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Law</item>
		</faculties>
		<postal_code type="str">Avenue du 30 Juin</postal_code>
		<telephone type="str"> +243 (97) 230 2443</telephone>
		<description type="str">Established in 2002,  Université Protestante de Lubumbashi (Protestant University of Lubumbashi) is a non-profit private higher-education institution located in the urban setting of the metropolis of Lubumbashi (population range of 1,000,000-5,000,000 inhabitants), Haut-Katanga.   Officially recognized by the Ministère de l'Enseignement Supérieur et Universitaire, République Démocratique du Congo (Ministry of Higher and University Education of the Democratic Republic of the Congo), Université Protestante de Lubumbashi (UPL) is a very small (uniRank enrollment range: 1,000-1,999 students) coeducational Congolese higher education institution formally affiliated with the Christian-Protestant religion. Université Protestante de Lubumbashi (UPL) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study matrix below for further details. This 18 years old Congolese higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations and students' past academic record and grades.  The admission rate range is 50-60% making this Congolese higher education organization a averagely selective institution. International applicants are eligible to apply for enrollment.  UPL also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including  sports facilities,  financial aids and/or scholarships,  as well as administrative services.</description>
		<name type="str">Protestant University of Lubumbashi</name>
		<acronym type="str">UPL</acronym>
		<founded type="str">2002</founded>
	</item>
	<item type="dict">
		<rank type="str">6</rank>
		<french_name type="str">Université Catholique du Congo</french_name>
		<location type="str">Kinshasa</location>
		<faculties type="null"/>
		<postal_code type="str">Avenue de l'Université n. 2; Boîte Postale 1534</postal_code>
		<telephone type="str"> +243 (81) 700 7985</telephone>
		<description type="str">Founded in 1957,  Université Catholique du Congo (Catholic University of Congo) is a  private higher-education institution located in the large metropolis of Kinshasa (population range of over 5,000,000 inhabitants).   Officially recognized by the Ministère de l'Enseignement Supérieur et Universitaire, République Démocratique du Congo (Ministry of Higher and University Education of the Democratic Republic of the Congo), Université Catholique du Congo (UCC) is a coeducational Congolese higher education institution formally affiliated with the Christian-Catholic religion. Université Catholique du Congo (UCC) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study matrix below for further details.  UCC also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library,  as well as administrative services.</description>
		<name type="str">Catholic University of Congo</name>
		<acronym type="str">UCC</acronym>
		<founded type="str">1957</founded>
	</item>
	<item type="dict">
		<rank type="str">7</rank>
		<french_name type="str">Université Officielle de Bukavu</french_name>
		<location type="str">Bukavu</location>
		<faculties type="list">
			<item type="str">Faculty of Medicine and Pharmacy </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Law </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Applied Sciences and Sciences </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Social, Political and Administrative Sciences </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Economics and Management </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Arts and Humanities</item>
		</faculties>
		<postal_code type="str"/>
		<telephone type="str"> +243 </telephone>
		<description type="str">Established in 2010,  Université Officielle de Bukavu (Official University of Bukavu) is a non-profit public higher-education institution located in the large city of Bukavu (population range of 500,000-1,000,000 inhabitants), South Kivu.   Officially recognized by the Ministère de l'Enseignement Supérieur et Universitaire, République Démocratique du Congo (Ministry of Higher and University Education of the Democratic Republic of the Congo), Université Officielle de Bukavu (UOB) is a coeducational Congolese higher education institution. Université Officielle de Bukavu (UOB) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as bachelor degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study matrix below for further details.  UOB also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library,  as well as administrative services.</description>
		<name type="str">Official University of Bukavu</name>
		<acronym type="str">UOB</acronym>
		<founded type="str">2010</founded>
	</item>
	<item type="dict">
		<rank type="str">8</rank>
		<french_name type="str">Université Catholique de Bukavu</french_name>
		<location type="str">Bukavu</location>
		<faculties type="list">
			<item type="str">Faculty of Architecture and Urbanism </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Agriculture </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Economics </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Law </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Medicine </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Sciences </item>
			<item type="str"> Faculty of Social Sciences</item>
		</faculties>
		<postal_code type="str">Bugabo 02, Avenue de la Mission, Commune de Kadutu</postal_code>
		<telephone type="str"> +243 854 893 440</telephone>
		<description type="str">Established in 1989,  Université Catholique de Bukavu (Catholic University of Bukavu) is a non-profit private higher-education institution located in the urban setting of the medium city of Bukavu (population range of 250,000-499,999 inhabitants), South Kivu.   Officially recognized by the Ministère de l'Enseignement Supérieur et Universitaire, République Démocratique du Congo (Ministry of Higher and University Education of the Democratic Republic of the Congo), Université Catholique de Bukavu (UCB) is a small (uniRank enrollment range: 3,000-3,999 students) coeducational Congolese higher education institution formally affiliated with the Christian-Catholic religion. Université Catholique de Bukavu (UCB) offers courses and programs leading to officially recognized higher education degrees such as pre-bachelor degrees (i.e. certificates, diplomas, associate or foundation), bachelor degrees, master degrees, doctorate degrees in several areas of study. See the uniRank degree levels and areas of study matrix below for further details. This 31 years old Congolese higher-education institution has a selective admission policy based on entrance examinations.  The admission rate range is 30-40% making this Congolese higher education organization a very selective institution. International applicants are eligible to apply for enrollment.  UCB also provides several academic and non-academic facilities and services to students including a library,  housing,  sports facilities,  financial aids and/or scholarships,  study abroad and exchange programs,  as well as administrative services.</description>
		<name type="str">Catholic University of Bukavu</name>
		<acronym type="str">UCB</acronym>
		<founded type="str">1989</founded>
	</item>
</root>
